A Hyperlink Crime-Drama
Country Hard is a crime film directed by Paul Utomi.
Country Hard is a hyperlink crime-drama that explores a day in the lives of seven strangers
as their paths interconnect in a way that may alter their lives forever.
Dinma, played by Kehinde Bankole.
Ochuko, played by Tope Tedela.
Chima, played by Timini Egbuson.
Tola, played by Omowunmi Dada.
Laide, played by Baaj Adebule.
Fadeke, played by Theresa Edem.
No Hard Feelings is a 2023 American sex comedy film starring Jennifer Lawrence as a woman hired by a wealthy
couple to romance their romantically and sexually inexperienced son, played by Andrew Barth Feldman.
The film is directed by Gene Stupnitsky from a
screenplay he co-wrote with John Phillips.
Along with Lawrence—who was one of the film's producers—and Feldman, the film
stars Laura Benanti, Natalie Morales, and Matthew Broderick.
The project was announced in October 2021, when Sony Pictures Releasing and Columbia Pictures
won a bidding war between Apple Original Films, Netflix and Universal Pictures.
Lawrence joined the cast and produced the film with
Stupnitsky attached to direct it.
Much of the cast joined in September to October 2022.
Filming began in late September in various Nassau County locations in the
New York City metropolitan area and finished in November.
No Hard Feelings was theatrically released in the United States
on June 23, 2023, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
It received positive reviews from critics and grossed over $87
million worldwide against a $45 million budget.
Lawrence earned a nomination for Best Actress in a Motion Picture – Comedy or Musical at the 81st Golden Globe
Awards, and won the Comedy Movie Star of the Year award at the 49th People's Choice Awards.
The film was nominated for Best Comedy at the 29th Critics' Choice Awards.